[{"answer": "Well, I probably thought it was kind of silly at the time.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Or how did that all come about?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "The older you get, yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Is it a hard thing to, you know, live up to all these years later?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Is it hard for you to watch?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Usually once.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Do you watch your own movies?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "I think it was a lot for me.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "How are you dealing with all this at that time?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "No, no, look.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "What are you going to torture me with now?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Any regrets about not taking those?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Early on I probably was, but -- I mean that changed pretty quickly.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "At that point were you worried about being typecast or pigeon holed in any way?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Is that OK?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "The whole thing was quite a task.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "What'd you have to do?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "It took -- I don't know.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "And how long does a process like that take?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Well, I think we're really compatible and just different enough to keep it interesting.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "What -- is there a key, a rule?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Did you use him as research?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "But you know this was 1993, right, when you did this?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "I mean was it a hard decision for you to adopt, you know, unmarried?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I mean, I think he was attracted to me.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "How could anyone be unsure about Michelle Pfeiffer?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Again, we have our sources.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Who'd you get that from?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "And I -- it just really, it just really changes everything, you know?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "I would be so lucky to have him be writing for me.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Would you work with your husband?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Really different.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "What's different about you?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Then?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "You know, I did some acupuncture.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Sometimes I do, sometimes I don't.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Is it something you think about?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "I mean, who cares, right?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "I mean just, the double standard that you hear about is it real?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "I mean, I'm still -- I mean, I'm never really a glutton, you know, I mean -- I mean, in terms of relative to maybe some other people, you know...", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Well, I actually really love the vegan diet because I love carbs.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "How hard is it?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "... for somebody who ate well and exercised well and did all the right things.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "It's really remarkable.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Stunning, right?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "Well, the thing is, you know -- look, I'm not an expert on any of this.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "And let's just ban, as Mayor Bloomberg has done in New York -- he's saying large product sales of that -- what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "But the fact that, you know, people are going to sort of now -- who wouldn't have paid attention before, are going to kind of sit up and go, Well, why would he want to do that?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "FEIFFER: Well, I would say what I did was I just said, OK, I'm just going to do -- I'm going to give myself eight weeks and I'm going to just -- I'm not going to commit to this for a lifetime because it's -- it's -- psychologically, it's huge for people to wrap their minds -- and just to see.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "Any tips on anyone who -- anyone that wants to start a vegan diet now watching you?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "They challenge you a little bit.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "But it also -- you know, it makes room for really interesting conversations now because they take me on, you know?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "It's the first time I've done this...", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "You like that?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "Well, I think she was probably most excited by the pageant just because in her lifetime, as in ours, she would never have seen anything quite like that.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "Which of all these do you think the queen will be most excited by, Katie?", "qSentId": 810}, {"answer": "I think absolutely.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120604pmt", "aSentId": 846, "question": "I mean, can you imagine?", "qSentId": 845}]